[{"answer": "I think he might be.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "I mean would you assume with your legal brain that he was making a point there?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I guess one of the things I'd want to know is the George Anthony factor, the father.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "If you were about to talk to him, Dan, what would you say to him?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "No, no, it was planned anyway.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Jeff Ashton, I mean, were you going to retire anyway, or has this kind of put you off the justice system?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, I think the reaction of all of us was we were pretty shocked, as everyone else was, but you know all of us have been doing this long enough to know that anytime you have a jury making a decision, you just never know what they're going to do.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What was your reaction when you realized it had gone the wrong way?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well, I think if this jury, you know, came to the verdict they did based upon the belief in something that wasn't in evidence.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What is the more likely premise now that this is all over, do you think?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think that the sentence necessarily is a comment on how the judge felt about the more serious charges.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Would you concur with that?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Well, you know, obviously, we thought the forensic evidence was there to establish her guilt of first-degree murder.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Was that the key problem here, that the forensic evidence just wasn't there for you to get a conviction?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we did what we could to prevent that, but the jury spoke and I believe the judge gave her the maximum sentence that he could.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "I mean, do you feel comfortable that someone who is a -- clearly a pathological liar, who was an appallingly negligent mother, if nothing else, clearly not, in my view, in any fit mental state, do you feel comfortable that somebody like that will be walking the streets of America in a few days' time?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, first of all, I should tell you that most of the people who watched this case thought that Jeff Ashton did a very good job as a prosecutor.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What did you make of what he said?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I happen to agree with you.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "It was -- it was the most censorious sentence he could have imposed?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "I absolutely think it's fair.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Is that fair, do you think?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "No, I don't believe they should.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Should they have charged on slightly lesser charges, do you think, or not?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "I do think there was a potential for overcharging.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Do you think that that was what wend wrong here?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I believe she was guilty of murder.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Let me ask you first, Stacey?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "I don't necessarily agree that it's first-degree murder.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Robin?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "No, not at all, given the good time laws and the way that most states work in releasing prisoners, I'm not surprised at all.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Were you surprised by how quickly Casey Anthony's being set free?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "That was a surprising part of it for me.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Well, will she have any restrictions on her when she walks through those gates out of prison?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I can tell you that I'm aware of the fact that this young lady was, in effect, tried in the court of public opinion long before the actual trial took place.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "What did you make of the events of the last 48 hours?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Look, this is a perfect example, this case, of while you're innocent until proven guilty in a court of law, you're guilty until proven innocent in the media.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What would you do?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I think it's a very complex family relationship.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Would you agree?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, all I can tell you is what all the arm chair quarterbacks have said over the last three years.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Unless you are the person who knows exactly what's happened to her?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "I think my gut tells me what it's been telling me for the last 250 or so trials that I've covered.", "docId": "110707pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "What does your gut tell you about this?", "qSentId": 491}]